{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 1, "故事": "欣欣今晚想去参加她朋友的聚会，但她肚子疼。她知道，如果她告诉妈妈她有肚子疼，她妈妈不会让她去的。她试图隐藏自己的感受，这样她妈妈就会让她去参加聚会了。", "问题": "欣欣真实的感受是怎么样？", "选项A": "A.悲伤", "选项B": "B.害怕", "选项C": "C.开心", "选项D": "D.失望", "STORY": "Xinxin wants to go to her friend's party tonight, but she has a stomachache. She knows, if she tells her mother she has a stomachache, her mother does not let her go. She tries to hide her feelings, so her mother lets her go to the party.", "QUESTION": "What are Xinxin's real feelings?", "OPTION-A": "Sad", "OPTION-B": "Scared", "OPTION-C": "Happy", "OPTION-D": "Disappointed", "答案\nANSWER": "A"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 2, "故事": "欣欣今晚想去参加她朋友的聚会，但她肚子疼。她知道，如果她告诉妈妈她有肚子疼，她妈妈不会让她去的。她试图隐藏自己的感受，这样她妈妈就会让她去参加聚会了。", "问题": "为什么欣欣真实感受是悲伤？", "选项A": "A. 因为她不喜欢聚会", "选项B": "B.因为肚子疼", "选项C": "C.她不能参加聚会了", "选项D": "D.因为害怕妈妈担心", "STORY": "Xinxin wants to go to her friend's party tonight, but she has a stomachache. She knows, if she tells her mother she has a stomachache, her mother does not let her go. She tries to hide her feelings, so her mother lets her go to the party.", "QUESTION": "Why is Xinxin's true feeling sad?", "OPTION-A": "Because she does not like parties", "OPTION-B": "Because of the stomachache", "OPTION-C": "She cannot attend the party", "OPTION-D": "Because she fears her mother worries", "答案\nANSWER": "B"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 3, "故事": "欣欣今晚想去参加她朋友的聚会，但她肚子疼。她知道，如果她告诉妈妈她有肚子疼，她妈妈不会让她去的。她试图隐藏自己的感受，这样她妈妈就会让她去参加聚会了。", "问题": "当欣欣发生这种事时，她表面看起来怎么样？", "选项A": "A.悲伤", "选项B": "B.害怕", "选项C": "C.开心", "选项D": "D.失望", "STORY": "Xinxin wants to go to her friend's party tonight, but she has a stomachache. She knows, if she tells her mother she has a stomachache, her mother does not let her go. She tries to hide her feelings, so her mother lets her go to the party.", "QUESTION": "How does Xinxin appear when this happens?", "OPTION-A": "Sad", "OPTION-B": "Scared", "OPTION-C": "Happy", "OPTION-D": "Disappointed", "答案\nANSWER": "C"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 4, "故事": "欣欣今晚想去参加她朋友的聚会，但她肚子疼。她知道，如果她告诉妈妈她有肚子疼，她妈妈不会让她去的。她试图隐藏自己的感受，这样她妈妈就会让她去参加聚会了。", "问题": "为什么欣欣表面看起来会开心", "选项A": "A.因为实话告诉妈妈她肚子疼，没有骗妈妈。", "选项B": "B.因为妈妈同意她参加聚会", "选项C": "C.为了避免妈妈不让参加聚会", "选项D": "D.因为她妈妈理解她的状况。", "STORY": "Xinxin wants to go to her friend's party tonight, but she has a stomachache. She knows, if she tells her mother she has a stomachache, her mother does not let her go. She tries to hide her feelings, so her mother lets her go to the party.", "QUESTION": "Why does Xinxin seem happy on the surface?", "OPTION-A": "Because she tells her mother the truth that she has a stomachache, she does not lie to her mother.", "OPTION-B": "Because her mother agrees to her attending the party", "OPTION-C": "To avoid her mother not letting her attend the party", "OPTION-D": "Because her mother understands her situation.", "答案\nANSWER": "C"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 1, "故事": "陈飞正在和朋友玩游戏。在游戏结束时，陈飞赢了，而他的朋友输了。陈飞试图隐藏他的真实感受，因为否则他的朋友可能不再和他玩。", "问题": "陈飞的真实感受是怎么样的？", "选项A": "A. 惊讶", "选项B": "B. 淡定", "选项C": "C. 高兴", "选项D": "D. 感激", "STORY": "Chen Fei is playing games with his friend. When the game ends, Chen Fei wins and his friend loses. Chen Fei tries to hide his real feelings, because otherwise his friend may not play with him anymore.", "QUESTION": "What are Chen Fei's real feelings?", "OPTION-A": "Surprised", "OPTION-B": "Calm", "OPTION-C": "Happy", "OPTION-D": "Grateful", "答案\nANSWER": "C"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 2, "故事": "陈飞正在和朋友玩游戏。在游戏结束时，陈飞赢了，而他的朋友输了。陈飞试图隐藏他的真实感受，因为否则他的朋友可能不再和他玩。", "问题": "为什么陈飞真实感受是开心？", "选项A": "A. 因为他赢了游戏", "选项B": "B. 因为他想让朋友感到开心", "选项C": "C. 因为他隐藏了真实感受", "选项D": "D. 因为他喜欢玩游戏", "STORY": "Chen Fei is playing games with his friend. When the game ends, Chen Fei wins and his friend loses. Chen Fei tries to hide his real feelings, because otherwise his friend may not play with him anymore.", "QUESTION": "Why is Chen Fei's real feeling happy?", "OPTION-A": "Because he wins the game", "OPTION-B": "Because he wants to make his friend happy", "OPTION-C": "Because he hides his real feelings", "OPTION-D": "Because he likes to play games", "答案\nANSWER": "A"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 3, "故事": "陈飞正在和朋友玩游戏。在游戏结束时，陈飞赢了，而他的朋友输了。陈飞试图隐藏他的真实感受，因为否则他的朋友可能不再和他玩。", "问题": "当陈飞发生这种事时，他表面看起来怎么样的？", "选项A": "A. 惊讶", "选项B": "B. 淡定", "选项C": "C. 高兴", "选项D": "D. 感激", "STORY": "Chen Fei is playing games with his friend. When the game ends, Chen Fei wins and his friend loses. Chen Fei tries to hide his real feelings, because otherwise his friend may not play with him anymore.", "QUESTION": "How does Chen Fei appear when this happens?", "OPTION-A": "Surprised", "OPTION-B": "Calm", "OPTION-C": "Happy", "OPTION-D": "Grateful", "答案\nANSWER": "B"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 4, "故事": "陈飞正在和朋友玩游戏。在游戏结束时，陈飞赢了，而他的朋友输了。陈飞试图隐藏他的真实感受，因为否则他的朋友可能不再和他玩。", "问题": "为什么陈飞表面看起来是淡定的？", "选项A": "A. 因为他不在意胜负", "选项B": "B. 因为他喜欢隐藏感情", "选项C": "C. 因为他觉得游戏不重要", "选项D": "D. 因为避免让朋友不悦", "STORY": "Chen Fei is playing games with his friend. When the game ends, Chen Fei wins and his friend loses. Chen Fei tries to hide his real feelings, because otherwise his friend may not play with him anymore.", "QUESTION": "Why does Chen Fei appear calm on the surface?", "OPTION-A": "Because he does not care about winning or losing", "OPTION-B": "Because he likes to hide his feelings", "OPTION-C": "Because he thinks the game is not important", "OPTION-D": "Because he avoids upsetting his friend", "答案\nANSWER": "D"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 1, "故事": "如如在学校参加一场演讲比赛。她在演讲中说错了一段话，而其他同学都表现得很出色。比赛结束后，同学们相互分享自己的表现，没有人犯任何错误。如如试图假装她的演讲做得和他们一样好", "问题": "如如的真实感受是怎么样的？", "选项A": "A. 开心", "选项B": "B. 难过", "选项C": "C. 自豪", "选项D": "D. 害怕", "STORY": "Ruru participates in a speech competition at school. She makes a mistake in her speech, and all other students perform very well. After the competition ends, the students share their performances with each other, no one makes any mistakes. Ruru tries to pretend her speech is as good as theirs", "QUESTION": "What are Ruru's real feelings?", "OPTION-A": "Happy", "OPTION-B": "Sad", "OPTION-C": "Proud", "OPTION-D": "Afraid", "答案\nANSWER": "B"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 2, "故事": "如如在学校参加一场演讲比赛。她在演讲中说错了一段话，而其他同学都表现得很出色。比赛结束后，同学们相互分享自己的表现，没有人犯任何错误。如如试图假装她的演讲做得和他们一样好", "问题": "为什么如如真实感受是难过的？", "选项A": "A. 因为在比赛中紧张导致难过", "选项B": "B. 因为她说错了一段话", "选项C": "C. 因为她不在乎比赛结果", "选项D": "D. 因为她想和同学一样出色", "STORY": "Ruru participates in a speech competition at school. She makes a mistake in her speech, and all other students perform very well. After the competition ends, the students share their performances with each other, no one makes any mistakes. Ruru tries to pretend her speech is as good as theirs", "QUESTION": "Why is Ruru's true feeling sad?", "OPTION-A": "Because she feels nervous in the competition", "OPTION-B": "Because she makes a mistake in her speech", "OPTION-C": "Because she does not care about the competition results", "OPTION-D": "Because she wants to be as excellent as her classmates", "答案\nANSWER": "B"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 3, "故事": "如如在学校参加一场演讲比赛。她在演讲中说错了一段话，而其他同学都表现得很出色。比赛结束后，同学们相互分享自己的表现，没有人犯任何错误。如如试图假装她的演讲做得和他们一样好", "问题": "当如如发生这种事时，她表面看起来怎么样的？", "选项A": "A. 开心", "选项B": "B. 难过", "选项C": "C. 自豪", "选项D": "D. 害怕", "STORY": "Ruru participates in a speech competition at school. She makes a mistake in her speech, and all other students perform very well. After the competition ends, the students share their performances with each other, no one makes any mistakes. Ruru tries to pretend her speech is as good as theirs", "QUESTION": "How does Ruru appear when this happens?", "OPTION-A": "Happy", "OPTION-B": "Sad", "OPTION-C": "Proud", "OPTION-D": "Afraid", "答案\nANSWER": "A"}
{"能力\nABILITY": "Emotion: Hidden emotions", "序号\nINDEX": 4, "故事": "如如在学校参加一场演讲比赛。她在演讲中说错了一段话，而其他同学都表现得很出色。比赛结束后，同学们相互分享自己的表现，没有人犯任何错误。如如试图假装她的演讲做得和他们一样好", "问题": "为什么如如表面看起来是开心的？", "选项A": "A. 因为她假装她演讲的跟同学们一样好", "选项B": "B. 因为她参加了学校演讲比赛，很开心", "选项C": "C. 因为她不在乎比赛结果", "选项D": "D. 因为她想和同学一样出色", "STORY": "Ruru participates in a speech competition at school. She makes a mistake in her speech, and all other students perform very well. After the competition ends, the students share their performances with each other, no one makes any mistakes. Ruru tries to pretend her speech is as good as theirs", "QUESTION": "Why does Ruru seem happy on the surface?", "OPTION-A": "Because she pretends her speech is as good as her classmates", "OPTION-B": "Because she participates in the school speech competition and is very happy", "OPTION-C": "Because she does not care about the competition results", "OPTION-D": "Because she wants to be as excellent as her classmates", "答案\nANSWER": "A"}
